<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-09-19T14:43:54-05:00</updated><id>/blog/feed.xml</id><title type="html">William Hatcher’s Blog</title><subtitle>A sporadic blog</subtitle><author><name>William Hatcher</name></author><entry><title type="html">Introduction &amp;amp; About the Author</title><link href="/blog/introduction" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Introduction &amp;amp; About the Author" /><published>2025-09-19T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2025-09-19T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/blog/introduction</id><content type="html" xml:base="/blog/introduction"><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to a sporadic blog about tech, life, education, and whatever else I want to write about.
<!--more--></p>

<h1 id="purpose--background">Purpose &amp; Background</h1>

<p>People have suggested I start documenting my exploits and technical <del>kludges</del> feats for several years. I don’t like the idea of sitting down to write - whether it’s technical documentation, journaling thoughts, or even class notes - so I put off detailing the fun and exciting things in writing which leads to details being forgotten and stories being lost.</p>

<p>There have been a few adventures my friends and I have done this year that I actually want people to know about. Let us, dear reader, embark on an adventure and journey of our own: experiencing William’s writing and hopeful improvement.</p>

<h1 id="expectations">Expectations</h1>

<p>This blog is labeled as “sporadic” for a reason, please don’t expect a regular posting schedule. I do, however, want to be diligent in writing about new adventures within a few months of them.</p>

<h2 id="use-of-ai">Use of AI</h2>

<p>I use AI fairly often to learn, research, and write. I do not want to use AI to write my posts. If AI content is included in my posts I will notate the usage near the end of the post.</p>

<h1 id="about-the-author">About the Author</h1>

<p>William Hatcher is an extroverted nerd who loves people and likes technology. He has a passion for networking, infrastructure, virtualization, and very old computers. His cheery demeanor, positive outlook, and thoughtful care along with his iconic hat leaves a lasting impression on many people.</p>

<p>With a BS in Computer Information Systems from East Texas A&amp;M University at RELLIS under his belt, he is currently a masters student at Texas A&amp;M University studying large-scale infrastructure and networking with plans to earn a PhD to pursue his dream of teaching at the collegiate level as a professor. He has several years of industry experience including founding and selling a company and Discord bot, Mr. Translate. You can find his publications on <a href="https://orcid.org/0009-0005-4441-2634">ORCID</a> or <a href="https://scholar.google.com/citations?user=iWsEgf0AAAAJ">Google Scholar</a>.</p>]]></content><author><name>William Hatcher</name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to a sporadic blog about tech, life, education, and whatever else I want to write about.]]></summary></entry></feed>